{
  "extraDescription": "NB: first operand is always divisible by second operand if second operand is not zero",
  "openingRemarks": "NB: You can enter 'U' or 'unexpected' for results which are not expected or defined",
  "questions": [
    {
      "question": "-28 &#xF7; -7",
      "answer": "4",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix"]
    },
    {
      "question": "20 &#xF7; 10",
      "answer": "2",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix"]
    },
    {
      "question": "18 &#xF7; 9",
      "answer": "2",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix"]
    },
    {
      "question": "28 &#xF7; -4",
      "answer": "-7",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix"]
    },
    {
      "question": "14 &#xF7; -2",
      "answer": "-7",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix"]
    },
    {
      "question": "28 &#xF7; -7",
      "answer": "-4",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix"]
    },
    {
      "question": "84 &#xF7; 12",
      "answer": "7",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix"]
    },
    {
      "question": "-12 &#xF7; -4",
      "answer": "3",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix"]
    },
    {
      "question": "-33 &#xF7; -3",
      "answer": "11",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix"]
    },
    {
      "question": "-96 &#xF7; 12",
      "answer": "-8",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix"]
    },
    {
      "question": "56 &#xF7; -8",
      "answer": "-7",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix"]
    },
    {
      "question": "12 &#xF7; 3",
      "answer": "4",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix"]
    },
    {
      "question": "-88 &#xF7; 8",
      "answer": "-11",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix"]
    },
    {
      "question": "-5 &#xF7; 5",
      "answer": "-1",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix"]
    },
    {
      "question": "2 &#xF7; 0",
      "expectedDenominators": [0],
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix"],
      "answer": "undefined"
    },
    {
      "question": "0 &#xF7; 2",
      "expectedDenominators": [0],
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix"],
      "answer": "0"
    },
    {
      "question": "45 &#xF7; 5",
      "answer": "9",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix"]
    },
    {
      "question": "0 &#xF7; 4",
      "expectedDenominators": [0],
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix"],
      "answer": "0"
    },
    {
      "question": "72 &#xF7; 9",
      "answer": "8",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix"]
    },
    {
      "question": "4 &#xF7; 4",
      "expectedDenominators": [0],
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix"],
      "answer": "1"
    },
    {
      "question": "-54 &#xF7; 6",
      "answer": "-9",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix"]
    },
    {
      "question": "72 &#xF7; -8",
      "answer": "-9",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix"]
    },
    {
      "question": "0 &#xF7; 0",
      "expectedDenominators": [0],
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix"],
      "answer": "undefined"
    },
    {
      "question": "80 &#xF7; -10",
      "answer": "-8",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix"]
    },
    {
      "question": "-21 &#xF7; 3",
      "answer": "-7",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix"]
    },
    {
      "question": "-36 &#xF7; -3",
      "answer": "12",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix"]
    },
    {
      "question": "3 &#xF7; 3",
      "expectedDenominators": [0],
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix"],
      "answer": "1"
    },
    {
      "question": "-1 &#xF7; 0",
      "expectedDenominators": [0],
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix"],
      "answer": "undefined"
    },
    {
      "question": "-3 &#xF7; 1",
      "expectedDenominators": [0],
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix"],
      "answer": "-3"
    },
    {
      "question": "-132 &#xF7; -12",
      "answer": "11",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix"]
    },
    {
      "question": "-20 &#xF7; 4",
      "answer": "-5",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix"]
    },
    {
      "question": "20 &#xF7; 5",
      "answer": "4",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix"]
    },
    {
      "question": "-55 &#xF7; -5",
      "answer": "11",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix"]
    },
    {
      "question": "12 &#xF7; -6",
      "answer": "-2",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix"]
    },
    {
      "question": "48 &#xF7; 6",
      "answer": "8",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix"]
    },
    {
      "question": "4 &#xF7; 0",
      "expectedDenominators": [0],
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix"],
      "answer": "undefined"
    },
    {
      "question": "-84 &#xF7; 7",
      "answer": "-12",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix"]
    },
    {
      "question": "1 &#xF7; 1",
      "expectedDenominators": [0],
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix"],
      "answer": "1"
    },
    {
      "question": "-3 &#xF7; 0",
      "expectedDenominators": [0],
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix"],
      "answer": "undefined"
    },
    {
      "question": "-2 &#xF7; 1",
      "expectedDenominators": [0],
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix"],
      "answer": "-2"
    },
    {
      "question": "96 &#xF7; -8",
      "answer": "-12",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix"]
    },
    {
      "question": "-4 &#xF7; 1",
      "expectedDenominators": [0],
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix"],
      "answer": "-4"
    },
    {
      "question": "20 &#xF7; -2",
      "answer": "-10",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix"]
    },
    {
      "question": "2 &#xF7; 2",
      "expectedDenominators": [0],
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix"],
      "answer": "1"
    },
    {
      "question": "144 &#xF7; 12",
      "answer": "12",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix"]
    },
    {
      "question": "0 &#xF7; 1",
      "expectedDenominators": [0],
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix"],
      "answer": "0"
    },
    {
      "question": "0 &#xF7; 3",
      "expectedDenominators": [0],
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix"],
      "answer": "0"
    },
    {
      "question": "-50 &#xF7; 10",
      "answer": "-5",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix"]
    },
    {
      "question": "-32 &#xF7; 8",
      "answer": "-4",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix"]
    },
    {
      "question": "36 &#xF7; -12",
      "answer": "-3",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix"]
    }
  ]
}
